[{"question":"/open_emoji/1F983.svg","correct_answer":"Turkey","incorrect_answers":["Chicken","Baby chick","Feather"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F983.svg","correct_answer":"Turkey","incorrect_answers":["Parrot","Hatching chick","Baby chick"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F423.svg","correct_answer":"Hatching chick","incorrect_answers":["Parrot","Baby chick","Chicken"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F414.svg","correct_answer":"Chicken","incorrect_answers":["Owl","Rooster","Turkey"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F986.svg","correct_answer":"Duck","incorrect_answers":["Baby chick","Owl","Rooster"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F427.svg","correct_answer":"Penguin","incorrect_answers":["Flamingo","Feather","Baby chick"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F989.svg","correct_answer":"Owl","incorrect_answers":["Baby chick","Penguin","Baby chick"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F426.svg","correct_answer":"Bird","incorrect_answers":["Flamingo","Chicken","Peacock"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F423.svg","correct_answer":"Hatching chick","incorrect_answers":["Turkey","Flamingo","Owl"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F986.svg","correct_answer":"Duck","incorrect_answers":["Hatching chick","Swan","Feather"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F9A9.svg","correct_answer":"Flamingo","incorrect_answers":["Swan","Duck","Hatching chick"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F985.svg","correct_answer":"Eagle","incorrect_answers":["Duck","Swan","Dove"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F413.svg","correct_answer":"Rooster","incorrect_answers":["Penguin","Parrot","Duck"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F989.svg","correct_answer":"Owl","incorrect_answers":["Rooster","Dove","Parrot"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F424.svg","correct_answer":"Baby chick","incorrect_answers":["Owl","Swan","Duck"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F424.svg","correct_answer":"Baby chick","incorrect_answers":["Swan","Duck","Eagle"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F40C.svg","correct_answer":"Snail","incorrect_answers":["Butterfly","Cricket","Microbe"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F98B.svg","correct_answer":"Butterfly","incorrect_answers":["Worm","Cricket","Snail"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1FAB1.svg","correct_answer":"Worm","incorrect_answers":["Mosquito","Butterfly","Ant"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F98B.svg","correct_answer":"Butterfly","incorrect_answers":["Snail","Spider","Lady beetle"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1FAB1.svg","correct_answer":"Worm","incorrect_answers":["Fly","Mosquito","Butterfly"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F41D.svg","correct_answer":"Honeybee","incorrect_answers":["Spider","Butterfly","Worm"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F41C.svg","correct_answer":"Ant","incorrect_answers":["Spider","Honeybee","Lady beetle"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F997.svg","correct_answer":"Cricket","incorrect_answers":["Honeybee","Fly","Spider"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F982.svg","correct_answer":"Scorpion","incorrect_answers":["Cricket","Fly","Honeybee"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F99F.svg","correct_answer":"Mosquito","incorrect_answers":["Microbe","Worm","Fly"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F982.svg","correct_answer":"Scorpion","incorrect_answers":["Mosquito","Microbe","Honeybee"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F98B.svg","correct_answer":"Butterfly","incorrect_answers":["Scorpion","Cricket","Honeybee"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F577.svg","correct_answer":"Spider","incorrect_answers":["Scorpion","Snail","Lady beetle"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F412.svg","correct_answer":"Monkey","incorrect_answers":["Pig","Gorilla","Deer"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F416.svg","correct_answer":"Pig","incorrect_answers":["Unicorn","Panda","Monkey"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F43C.svg","correct_answer":"Panda","incorrect_answers":["Tiger","Gorilla","Unicorn"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F98D.svg","correct_answer":"Gorilla","incorrect_answers":["Tiger","Rhinoceros","Panda"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F412.svg","correct_answer":"Monkey","incorrect_answers":["Horse","Cow","Raccoon"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F405.svg","correct_answer":"Tiger","incorrect_answers":["Rat","Horse","Llama"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F404.svg","correct_answer":"Cow","incorrect_answers":["Hedgehog","Llama","Leopard"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F98A.svg","correct_answer":"Fox","incorrect_answers":["Rabbit","Camel","Goat"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F402.svg","correct_answer":"Ox","incorrect_answers":["Camel","Water buffalo","Leopard"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F998.svg","correct_answer":"Kangaroo","incorrect_answers":["Gorilla","Hamster","Ox"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F987.svg","correct_answer":"Bat","incorrect_answers":["Ewe","Ox","Badger"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F981.svg","correct_answer":"Lion","incorrect_answers":["Badger","Polar bear","Ram"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F405.svg","correct_answer":"Tiger","incorrect_answers":["Polar bear","Orangutan","Ram"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F40E.svg","correct_answer":"Horse","incorrect_answers":["Giraffe","Polar bear","Gorilla"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F994.svg","correct_answer":"Hedgehog","incorrect_answers":["Giraffe","Polar bear","Gorilla"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F9A1.svg","correct_answer":"Badger","incorrect_answers":["Zebra","Giraffe","Monkey"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F407.svg","correct_answer":"Rabbit","incorrect_answers":["Cow","Bear","Giraffe"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F417.svg","correct_answer":"Boar","incorrect_answers":["Camel","Otter","Skunk"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F411.svg","correct_answer":"Ewe","incorrect_answers":["Camel","Tiger","Koala"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F40E.svg","correct_answer":"Horse","incorrect_answers":["Skunk","Black cat","Zebra"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F417.svg","correct_answer":"Boar","incorrect_answers":["Rhinoceros","Ox","Skunk"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F417.svg","correct_answer":"Boar","incorrect_answers":["Goat","Rhinoceros","Unicorn"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F408.svg","correct_answer":"Cat","incorrect_answers":["Koala","Hippopotamus","Fox"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F42B.svg","correct_answer":"Camel","incorrect_answers":["Fox","Deer","Bat"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F405.svg","correct_answer":"Tiger","incorrect_answers":["Fox","Ox","Goat"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F415.svg","correct_answer":"Dog","incorrect_answers":["Bat","Mouse","Deer"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F994.svg","correct_answer":"Hedgehog","incorrect_answers":["Chipmunk","Black cat","Giraffe"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F994.svg","correct_answer":"Hedgehog","incorrect_answers":["Orangutan","Chipmunk","Kangaroo"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F405.svg","correct_answer":"Tiger","incorrect_answers":["Leopard","Hippopotamus","Giraffe"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F98F.svg","correct_answer":"Rhinoceros","incorrect_answers":["Giraffe","Cat","Hippopotamus"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F43C.svg","correct_answer":"Panda","incorrect_answers":["Giraffe","Water buffalo","Leopard"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F998.svg","correct_answer":"Kangaroo","incorrect_answers":["Leopard","Cat","Goat"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F43C.svg","correct_answer":"Panda","incorrect_answers":["Rhinoceros","Rabbit","Pig"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F402.svg","correct_answer":"Ox","incorrect_answers":["Llama","Goat","Chipmunk"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F98A.svg","correct_answer":"Fox","incorrect_answers":["Koala","Polar bear","Orangutan"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F998.svg","correct_answer":"Kangaroo","incorrect_answers":["Koala","Polar bear","Camel"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F9A8.svg","correct_answer":"Skunk","incorrect_answers":["Kangaroo","Mouse","Polar bear"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F410.svg","correct_answer":"Goat","incorrect_answers":["Leopard","Badger","Rat"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F987.svg","correct_answer":"Bat","incorrect_answers":["Poodle","Leopard","Rabbit"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F404.svg","correct_answer":"Cow","incorrect_answers":["Monkey","Leopard","Camel"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F418.svg","correct_answer":"Elephant","incorrect_answers":["Kangaroo","Ox","Rat"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F408.svg","correct_answer":"Cat","incorrect_answers":["Bat","Fox","Ram"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F993.svg","correct_answer":"Zebra","incorrect_answers":["Ram","Kangaroo","Wolf"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F40E.svg","correct_answer":"Horse","incorrect_answers":["Chipmunk","Bear","Lion"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F9A7.svg","correct_answer":"Orangutan","incorrect_answers":["Chipmunk","Hedgehog","Panda"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F98A.svg","correct_answer":"Fox","incorrect_answers":["Elephant","Chipmunk","Monkey"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F9A7.svg","correct_answer":"Orangutan","incorrect_answers":["Hedgehog","Ewe","Sloth"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F43B-200D-2744-FE0F.svg","correct_answer":"Polar bear","incorrect_answers":["Hedgehog","Elephant","Wolf"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F433.svg","correct_answer":"Whale","incorrect_answers":["Fish","Blowfish","Dolphin"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F419.svg","correct_answer":"Octopus","incorrect_answers":["Fish","Whale","Whale"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F41F.svg","correct_answer":"Fish","incorrect_answers":["Whale","Dolphin","Blowfish"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F421.svg","correct_answer":"Blowfish","incorrect_answers":["Fish","Tropical fish","Whale"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F988.svg","correct_answer":"Shark","incorrect_answers":["Whale","Octopus","Fish"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F420.svg","correct_answer":"Tropical fish","incorrect_answers":["Blowfish","Whale","Octopus"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F420.svg","correct_answer":"Tropical fish","incorrect_answers":["Blowfish","Whale","Octopus"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F40A.svg","correct_answer":"Crocodile","incorrect_answers":["Lizard","Dragon","Snake"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F40A.svg","correct_answer":"Crocodile","incorrect_answers":["T-Rex","Sauropod","Lizard"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F995.svg","correct_answer":"Sauropod","incorrect_answers":["Dragon","Snake","Turtle"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F40D.svg","correct_answer":"Snake","incorrect_answers":["T-Rex","Lizard","Turtle"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F40A.svg","correct_answer":"Crocodile","incorrect_answers":["Snake","Dragon","T-Rex"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F98E.svg","correct_answer":"Lizard","incorrect_answers":["Turtle","Sauropod","Snake"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F98E.svg","correct_answer":"Lizard","incorrect_answers":["Dragon","Snake","Sauropod"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F347.svg","correct_answer":"Grapes","incorrect_answers":["Watermelon","Tangerine","Broccoli"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F349.svg","correct_answer":"Watermelon","incorrect_answers":["Tomato","Hot dog","Blueberries"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F349.svg","correct_answer":"Watermelon","incorrect_answers":["Cherries","Tomato","Hot dog"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F349.svg","correct_answer":"Watermelon","incorrect_answers":["Cherries","Bagel","Peach"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F9C5.svg","correct_answer":"Onion","incorrect_answers":["Watermelon","Cherries","Stuffed flatbread"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F351.svg","correct_answer":"Peach","incorrect_answers":["Onion","Bagel","Hamburger"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F951.svg","correct_answer":"Avocado","incorrect_answers":["Blueberries","Bell pepper","Mushroom"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F959.svg","correct_answer":"Stuffed flatbread","incorrect_answers":["Bacon","Melon","Meat on bone"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F9C5.svg","correct_answer":"Onion","incorrect_answers":["Tomato","Potato","Mango"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F34A.svg","correct_answer":"Tangerine","incorrect_answers":["Meat on bone","Chestnut","Strawberry"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F345.svg","correct_answer":"Tomato","incorrect_answers":["Broccoli","Bell pepper","Pineapple"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F353.svg","correct_answer":"Strawberry","incorrect_answers":["Broccoli","Tamale","Stuffed flatbread"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F34B.svg","correct_answer":"Lemon","incorrect_answers":["Garlic","Peanuts","Bacon"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F344.svg","correct_answer":"Mushroom","incorrect_answers":["Garlic","Hot pepper","Grapes"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F969.svg","correct_answer":"Cut of meat","incorrect_answers":["Red apple","Broccoli","Poultry leg"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1FAD0.svg","correct_answer":"Blueberries","incorrect_answers":["French fries","Red apple","Stuffed flatbread"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F336.svg","correct_answer":"Hot pepper","incorrect_answers":["French fries","Broccoli","Blueberries"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F348.svg","correct_answer":"Melon","incorrect_answers":["Hot dog","Blueberries","Cut of meat"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F35F.svg","correct_answer":"French fries","incorrect_answers":["Broccoli","Blueberries","Taco"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F34D.svg","correct_answer":"Pineapple","incorrect_answers":["Hot dog","Lemon","Broccoli"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F96D.svg","correct_answer":"Mango","incorrect_answers":["Hot dog","Pretzel","Taco"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F336.svg","correct_answer":"Hot pepper","incorrect_answers":["Mango","Mushroom","Chestnut"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F956.svg","correct_answer":"Baguette bread","incorrect_answers":["Hot dog","Watermelon","Red apple"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F351.svg","correct_answer":"Peach","incorrect_answers":["Chestnut","Green apple","Cucumber"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F95D.svg","correct_answer":"Kiwi fruit","incorrect_answers":["Chestnut","Green apple","Peach"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F34A.svg","correct_answer":"Tangerine","incorrect_answers":["Hamburger","Cherries","Pizza"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F96F.svg","correct_answer":"Bagel","incorrect_answers":["Melon","Tomato","Poultry leg"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F34D.svg","correct_answer":"Pineapple","incorrect_answers":["Pizza","Melon","Hot pepper"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F955.svg","correct_answer":"Carrot","incorrect_answers":["Bell pepper","Banana","Red apple"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F346.svg","correct_answer":"Eggplant","incorrect_answers":["Banana","Green apple","Broccoli"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F95E.svg","correct_answer":"Pancakes","incorrect_answers":["Red apple","Olive","Melon"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F32D.svg","correct_answer":"Hot dog","incorrect_answers":["Baguette bread","Cherries","Green apple"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F952.svg","correct_answer":"Cucumber","incorrect_answers":["Potato","Tomato","Broccoli"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F35E.svg","correct_answer":"Bread","incorrect_answers":["Potato","Melon","Pretzel"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1FAD0.svg","correct_answer":"Blueberries","incorrect_answers":["Meat on bone","Red apple","Poultry leg"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F95E.svg","correct_answer":"Pancakes","incorrect_answers":["Eggplant","Meat on bone","Cherries"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F34F.svg","correct_answer":"Green apple","incorrect_answers":["Bread","French fries","Cherries"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1FAD1.svg","correct_answer":"Bell pepper","incorrect_answers":["French fries","Waffle","Ear of corn"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F956.svg","correct_answer":"Baguette bread","incorrect_answers":["Bread","Pineapple","Waffle"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F950.svg","correct_answer":"Croissant","incorrect_answers":["Onion","Green apple","Bread"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F351.svg","correct_answer":"Peach","incorrect_answers":["Strawberry","Banana","Onion"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F345.svg","correct_answer":"Tomato","incorrect_answers":["Blueberries","Banana","Pancakes"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F9C0.svg","correct_answer":"Cheese wedge","incorrect_answers":["Pancakes","Strawberry","Burrito"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1FAD3.svg","correct_answer":"Flatbread","incorrect_answers":["Mango","Pancakes","Strawberry"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F34F.svg","correct_answer":"Green apple","incorrect_answers":["Cut of meat","Lemon","Flatbread"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F9C0.svg","correct_answer":"Cheese wedge","incorrect_answers":["Cut of meat","Mushroom","Bagel"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F348.svg","correct_answer":"Melon","incorrect_answers":["Bagel","French fries","Pineapple"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F357.svg","correct_answer":"Poultry leg","incorrect_answers":["Bagel","Green apple","Pineapple"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F330.svg","correct_answer":"Chestnut","incorrect_answers":["Baguette bread","Hamburger","Flatbread"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F353.svg","correct_answer":"Strawberry","incorrect_answers":["Green apple","Waffle","Hamburger"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1FAD4.svg","correct_answer":"Tamale","incorrect_answers":["Baguette bread","Avocado","Bell pepper"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F952.svg","correct_answer":"Cucumber","incorrect_answers":["Cheese wedge","Green apple","Avocado"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F351.svg","correct_answer":"Peach","incorrect_answers":["Hot dog","Garlic","Tomato"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F350.svg","correct_answer":"Pear","incorrect_answers":["Red apple","Melon","Broccoli"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F351.svg","correct_answer":"Peach","incorrect_answers":["Baguette bread","Carrot","Cut of meat"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1FAD0.svg","correct_answer":"Blueberries","incorrect_answers":["Baguette bread","Carrot","Tangerine"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F340.svg","correct_answer":"Four leaf clover","incorrect_answers":["Flower","Herb","Rose"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F33F.svg","correct_answer":"Herb","incorrect_answers":["Maple leaf","Tulip","Flower"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F340.svg","correct_answer":"Four leaf clover","incorrect_answers":["Maple leaf","Flower","Cactus"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F3F5.svg","correct_answer":"Rosette","incorrect_answers":["Tulip","Rose","Flower"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F3F5.svg","correct_answer":"Rosette","incorrect_answers":["Maple leaf","Flower","Tulip"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F33B.svg","correct_answer":"Sunflower","incorrect_answers":["Maple leaf","Herb","Flower"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F339.svg","correct_answer":"Rose","incorrect_answers":["Shamrock","Cactus","Rosette"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F490.svg","correct_answer":"Flower","incorrect_answers":["Maple leaf","Four leaf clover","Wilted flower"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F33F.svg","correct_answer":"Herb","incorrect_answers":["Four leaf clover","Shamrock","Rose"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F33A.svg","correct_answer":"Flower","incorrect_answers":["Herb","Maple leaf","Four leaf clover"]},{"question":"/open_emoji/1F3F5.svg","correct_answer":"Rosette","incorrect_answers":["Herb","Shamrock","Wilted flower"]}]